Contact

M-3 Abdullah arcade, Street no#9, Block H North nazimabad. 03332179695 (Home) haxandawood98@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hasan-dawood-603188173 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Computer Science Management

Hasan Dawood

Freelance | Front end | Back end | HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | Node JS | Mongo DB | ASP .NET | Microsoft Sql | No Sql | My Sql | Postman

Karāchi

Summary

Experienced Member Technical with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Computer Science, Google Cloud Platform, and Management. Strong engineering professional graduated from PAF-Karachi Institute of Economics & Technology.

Experience

Google Developers
Core Member (Technical)
August 2019 - May 2020 (10 months)
PAF-KIET

Working as a core member of DSC team at PAF-KIET, empowering students with Google Products.

Smurf Universe
Customer Service Specialist
September 2017 - August 2019 (2 years)

Education

PAF-Karachi Institute of Economics & Technology Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Certification